Guide to the Southern Conferences on Women's History annual conference records, 1989-1997 UA 209
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Southern Conferences on Women's History annual conference records
1989-1997
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Boles, John B.
UA 209
0.75 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
The Southern Association for Women Historians presents an annual meeting known as the Southern Conference of Women's History. These annual conference records are predominantly from the conference held at Rice University in Houston, Texas from June 2-5, 1994. Records include planning documents, correspondence, surveys and realia that date from 1989-1997.
Biographical / Historical
The Southern Association for Women Historians presents an annual meeting known as the Southern Conference of Women's History.
Scope and Content
Records from the Southern Conferences on Women's History of the Southern Association for Women Historians. Predominantly from the conference held at Rice University in Houston, Texas from June 2-5, 1994. Records include planning documents, correspondence, surveys and realia that date from 1989-1997. These include follow up materials from the 2nd annual conference held Chapel Hill, N.C. in 1991 and planning information for the 4th annual conference held in Charleston, S.C. in 1997.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Papers donated by John B. Boles, the William P. Hobby professor of history at Rice University and editor of the Journal of Southern History.
Index Terms
Subjects
Women; Universities and colleges
Document Types
documents; letters (correspondence); memorabilia
Subjects (Persons)
Boles, John B.
- Series I: Annual conference records, 146053
  - 2nd annual conference, Chapel Hill, NC, June 7-8, 1991, 111560 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Conference Planning (1), 1992-1994, 111561 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Conference Planning (2), 1992-1994, 111562 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Conference Planning - Correspondence, 1991-1994, 111563 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1994, 111564 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Conference Materials, 1994, 111565 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Conference Expenses, 1994, 111566 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Conference Survey Results, 1994, 111567 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Conference Reports and Thank You's, 1994, 111568 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 4th Annual Conference, Charleston, S.C. (Planning), June 11-14, 1997, 111569 (Box 2, Folder 5)